Finding Aid to the Nancy Stoller Papers, 1981-1995 MSS 2000-6
University of California, San Francisco Archives & Special Collections
- Ephemera, 1983-1995; Series 5; 30 Folders: Carton 8 Folders 8/16-8/44; Container 9 Oversized Folder
  - Posters and Oversized Materials, 1984-1992; undated; Subseries 5.3; Container 9 - 1 oversized folder
    - Set of 5 different posters with duplicates of two of them (7 total) - South Africa "Township AIDS Project, Lesbian and Gay Programme, Johannesburg, South Africa" - All Gay Male - One shows sex in progress (w/condom) and suggests one "sodomize safely", undated (Carton 9, Folder 1)
    - SF AIDS Foundation - 1 fold-out flyer with poster center on "excuses for unsafe sex" Front when folded "An Important Message for Gay & Bisexual Men", undated (Carton 9, Folder 2)
    - Set of 6 different posters with duplicates - one in Spanish (12 total) - From "America Responds to AIDS" a joint project of the DHHS, Public Health Service, & CDC, undated (Carton 9, Folder 3)
    - 1 fold out flyer/catalog for pamphlets/fotonovela and other AIDS related documents from Network Publications/ETR Associates from Santa Cruz - some of which are in the pamphlet subseries, circa 1989 (Carton 9, Folder 4)
    - Centerfold Poster from Talk talk: a newsletter about AIDS: a supplement to Positive Outlook, No. 2 - Autumn 1995. "Who can get AIDS/Anyone can get AIDS?" (Carton 9, Folder 5)
    - Fold out Poster/Pamphlet from the AIDS Law Project (South Africa). Poster on "Confidentiality Rules! HIV and Human Rights" Also labeled HIV and Human Rights Pamphlet 3, January 1995 (Carton 9, Folder 6)
    - "None of these will give you AIDS." Poster from the AIDS Institute, New York State Health Department (Carton 9, Folder 7)
    - Foldout colored pictorial map/advertisement for Rockey/Raleigh Street, in Johannesburg, South Africa, 1995 (Carton 9, Folder 8)
    - Love Carefully ... Stop AIDS: A Free Conference for Women" (Portland, Oregon), February 14, 1987 (Carton 9, Folder 9)
    - "How to Have Safe Sex During the Epidemic" San Diego AIDS Project, undated (Carton 9, Folder 10)
    - Foldout flyer/donation form for "Coming Home: Supportive Services for Lesbians and Gay Men Facing Life Threatening Illness", undated (Carton 9, Folder 11)
    - Set of 3 posters from ADAPT (Funded by New York City Dept. of Health) "Basically AIDS = Death", circa 1984/85 (Carton 9, Folder 12)
    - Flyer/Poster for the bay area premiere of "Absolutely Positive" a documentary film, circa 1991 (Carton 9, Folder 13)
    - Flyer/poster for "Creating Safety, Valuing Diversity: Lesbians and Gay Men in the University and Society" a series of events presented by the President's Task Force on Lesbian and Gay Concerns of the University of Oregon, April 1991 (Carton 9, Folder 14)
    - Small Poster. "Tell Your Kids About AIDS Now. Or Someone Else May Have To Later" from The State of California AIDS Education Campaign: AIDS It's Up To You, undated (Carton 9, Folder 15)
    - Women & Children Plan (handwritten on butcher paper) - from SFAF: Education - Planning folder, 1986-1987 (Carton 9, Folder 16)